Everyone breaks.
Trigger Point is a action, thriller, mystery film directed by Brad Turner.
Nicolas Shaw is a retired U.S.
special operative who becomes part of an elite 'invisible' team that
quietly takes out the worst villains around the world.
Nicolas Shaw, played by Barry Pepper.
Fiona Snow, played by Laura Vandervoort.
Elias Kane, played by Colm Feore.
Monica Kane, played by Eve Harlow.
Mouthpiece, played by Rainbow Sun Francks.
Irene Cole, played by Jayne Eastwood.
Trigger Point is a 2021 Canadian action-thriller film directed by Brad Turner.
It stars Barry Pepper, Eve Harlow, Carlo Rota, Laura Vandervoort, Jayne Eastwood,
Nazneen Contractor, Greg Bryk, Rainbow Sun Francks, and Colm Feore.
The plot follows a retired special operative who returns to the
organization to help his former boss find his missing daughter.
Trigger Point was theatrically released by Screen Media Films on April 16, 2021.
The film was met with negative reviews from critics.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.